>> Jem Young: 另一个是， Nginx 的另一个是添加子域。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The other one is, another
thing with Nginx is adding a subdomain.
昨天我们为服务器创建了一个服务器块
Yesterday we created a server block for
our servers, and
这就是所谓的虚拟主机。
that's what's known as a virtual host.
所以我可以创造十个不同的领域
So I could create ten
different domains and
在一个 Nginx 配置上十个不同的服务器。
ten different servers on
one Nginx configuration.
根据我试图击中的 URL
And depending on the url
that I'm trying to hit,
内克斯会把我重定向到正确的地方
Nginx will redirect me to the right place.
因此，在这种情况下，我创建了一个名为test.j发射台的子域。
So in this case I created a subdomain
called test.jemisthe.best.
还有边便条，我后悔做 jem 是最好的，因为它没滚
And a side note, I regret doing jem is
the best because it just doesn't roll off
像 jem.party的舌头
the tongue like jem.party.
也许在 V3 我会做 jem.party
Maybe in V3 I'll do jem.party.
或者杰姆知道怎么派对我不知道
Or Jem knows how to party, I don't know.
但 Nginx 的伟大是我们可以像我们想要的那么多的领域。
But what's great about Nginx is we
can have as many domains as we want.
我们可以拥有尽可能多的服务器
And we can have as many
servers as we want,
因为从你的心理模型来看，这是它自己的一个服务器。
because in terms of your mental model,
this is a server on its own.
在编程方面，这是一个单独的服务器。
In terms of programming,
this is a server on its own.
在花钱的情况下，只有一台服务器。
In terms of paying for money,
you only have one server.
太棒了 这里有无限的服务器可用。
So that's great.
You have infinite servers here available.
稍后，我们将创建一个类似的子域。
Later in the course, we're going to
create a subdomain just like this.
我们要把它管到我们的服务器上。
And we're going to pipe it to our server.
然后我们就会创建一个应用程序
And then we're going to create
an application that just lives on that
而不是我们的主域
subdomain rather than our main domain.
但现在，这就是你的一个子领域，而不是太艰难。
But for now, this is how you had
a subdomain in, not too hard.
有什么问题吗
Any questions on this?
因为这很重要
Because this is kind of important.
但我们可以稍后再参考。
But we can reference back later.
如果你想知道这双冒号是什么
And if you're wondering
what these double colon and
支架也不是笑脸
brackets, it's not really a smiley face.
我不知道我在想如果有一个能匹配的情绪
I don't know, It's, I'm trying to think
if there's an emoji that matches this,
有两个戴着帽子和胡子的人
two people with a hat and a beard.
我不知道我不知道
I don't know.
这只是 IPv6 的注音
That's just IPv6 notation.
还记得昨天我们学到了因为我们的 IP 地址用完了
Remember yesterday we learned that
because we ran out of IP addresses,
我们必须创建 IPv6 ，这将为我们提供 304 个不消零的数字，这就是一堆零。
we had to create IPv6, which would give us
304 undecillion, which is a lot of zeros.
我记得这个事实
And the fact that I remembered that, but
我不记得要怎么做才知道我不是完美的
I can't remember how to properly do
a find just shows you I'm not perfect.